fashion-networks.com 2013-09-03

# Privacy Policy - apparel garment fashion networking textile retail job news

**  
Last Updated: May, 2009**

Your privacy is our top concern. We work hard to earn and keep your trust, so we adhere to the following principles to protect your privacy:

• We will never rent or sell your personally identifiable information to third parties for marketing purposes   
• We will never share your contact information with another user, without your consent.   
• Any sensitive information that you provide will be secured with all industry standard protocols and technology 

Notice of all changes that materially affect ways in which your personally identifiable data may be used or shared will be posted in updates to our Privacy Policy. If you continue to use the Fashion Networks service after notice of changes have been sent to you or published on our site, you hereby provide your consent to the changed practices.  
The following explains in details all aspects related to the privacy policy:

The mission of Fashion Networks is to enable individuals and organizations establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site www.fashion-networks.com. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we have agreed to disclose our privacy practices and have them reviewed for compliance.  
If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Fashion Networks by email at legalinfo@fashion-networks.com. 

**Information Collection**

_**Registration:**_  
In order to become a Fashion Networks user, you must first create an account on this web site. To create an account you are required to provide the following contact information: name, email address, your industry and choose a password. Because Fashion Networks is designed specifically for the soft goods industry, entries from people other than those related to the soft goods industry and those mentioned in the registration page are not recommended.  
Profile Information:

Once a user, you may provide additional information in the Profile section describing your skills, professional experiences, and networking objectives. Providing additional information beyond what is required at registration is entirely optional, but enables you to better identify yourself and find new opportunities in the Fashion Networks system.

_**Information about your Contacts**_  
In order to invite others to connect with you directly in Fashion Networks, you will enter their email addresses. This information will be used by Fashion Networks to send your invitation including a message that you write. The names and email addresses of people that you invite will be used only to send your invitation and reminders.

You may also choose to enter or upload contact data like address , phone number & fax number into your profile of our website. All this information entered there will only be viewable by you and will not be searchable by others in the Fashion Networks network without your permission.

All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own personally identifiable information.

_**Cookies & Log Files:**_  
Like most web sites, Fashion Networks uses cookies and web log files to track site usage. A cookie is a tiny data file which resides on your computer which allows Fashion Networks to recognize you as a user when you return to our site using the same computer and web browser. Unfortunately, if your browser settings do not allow cookies, you will not be able to use our website. Like the information you enter at registration or in your Profile, cookie and log file data is used to customize your experience on the web site.

Due to the communications standards on the Internet, when you visit the Fashion Networks web site we automatically receive the URL of the site from which you came and the site to which you are going when you leave Fashion Networks. We also receive the Internet protocol (IP) address of your computer (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system and type of web browser you are using, as well as the name of your ISP. This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the Fashion Networks service. The linkage between your IP address and your personally identifiable information is never shared with third-parties without your permission or except when required by law.

_**Web Beacons:**_   
We will allow other companies, called ad networks, to serve advertisements to Fashion Networks users. Ad networks include third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors and research firms. Fashion Networks may “target” some ads to users that fit a certain general profile — for example, “product managers in Texas.” Fashion Networks does NOT use personally identifiable information to target ads.

To deliver these ads properly, Fashion Networks may include a file, called a web beacon, from these ad networks within pages served by Fashion Networks so the networks may provide anonymized, aggregated auditing, research and reporting for advertisers as well as to target ads to you while you visit other websites.

Because your web browser must request these advertisements and web beacons from the ad network’s servers, these companies can view, edit or set their own cookies, just as if you had requested a web page from their site.  
These general targets may also be used by ad networks to display targeted ads on other websites as a substitute for random, irrelevant ads. You will never see additional ads as a result of being a Fashion Networks user and Fashion Networks never provides personally identifiable information to any advertiser nor any third party.

**Information Use**

Fashion Networks is an online service dedicated to helping all professionals and aspirants in the soft goods industry more effectively connect with one another. The personally identifiable information you choose to provide on this site is used to help you describe yourself to other users. This information can be utilized by Fashion Networks in such manner as Fashion Networks, in its sole discretion, deems appropriate.

_**Communications:**_  
Fashion Networks will communicate with you through email and notices posted on this website. Please be aware that you will always receive certain emails from Fashion Networks related to the proper functioning of your account, such as email notices when another user in your network sends you an opportunity. Fashion Networks may send you promotional information unless you have opted out of receiving such information. If you wish to opt-out of receiving promotional emails, you would be provided a linked for discontinuing subscription.

_**Customized Content:**_  
Information you provide at the time of registration or in your Profile section is also used to customize your experience on the web site. For example, when you login to your account we will display the screen names of new users who have recently joined your network.

**Information Sharing**

_**Sharing Information With Third Parties:**_  
Fashion Networks takes the privacy of our users very seriously. We will never sell, rent, or otherwise provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for marketing purposes. We will only share your personally identifiable with third parties to carry out your instructions and to provide specific services. For instance, if we request payment through a credit card, we would use a credit card processing company to bill users for subscription fees. These third parties would not retain, share, or store any personally identifiable information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements which limit their use of such information.

Fashion Networks does not display all information from a member’s profile to other members. Information like Contact Address, Phone Number & Fax Number are not displayed to other members. Users may/may not enter these details. However Fashion Networks does not warrant how third-party search engines will update their cache. All other details of the profile are displayed.

We may provide aggregated data about the usage of our services to third-parties for such purposes as we deem, in our sole discretion, to be appropriate. We may segment our users by Designation, Industry, Education, Company, and Geographical Location. 

_**Communications between Users:**_  
Many emails you initiate through Fashion Networks, an invitation sent to a non-user for instance, will not list your email address. However you name would be displayed in the communication mail. However e-mails send from Fashion Networks to other members will contain your e-mail address. Your contact information will only be shared with another user if both of you are members of Fashion Networks

_**Legal Disclaimer:**_  
It is possible that we may need to disclose personal information when required by law. We will disclose such information wherein we have a good-faith belief that it is necessary to comply with a court order, ongoing judicial proceeding, or other legal process served on our company or to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

**Accessing and Changing Your Account Information**

You can review the personal information you provided us and make any desired changes to the information, or to the settings for your Fashion Networks account, at any time by logging in to your account on the Fashion Networks website and editing the information on your Profile page. You can also close your account through the Fashion Networks website by intimating the administrator. When your account is closed, your name and other personally identifiable information would be removed from our publicly viewable data. We may retain certain data contributed by you if it may be necessary to prevent fraud or future abuse, or for legitimate business purposes, such as analysis of aggregated, non-personally-identifiable data, account recovery, or if required by law. All retained data will continue to be subject to the terms of the Fashion Networks Privacy Policy that you have previously agreed to. 

**Security**

In order to secure your personal information, access to your data on Fashion Networks is password-protected and sensitive data, if any (such as credit card information) is protected by encryption when it is exchanged between your web browser and our web site. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Fashion Networks may update this privacy policy. In the event there are significant changes in the way we treat your personally identifiable information, we will display a notice on this site. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
